wordsjournal.com 2010-12-25

# Privacy Policy – GoldStrikePoker.com

Thank you for reviewing our Privacy Policy.  
Your online safety is of utmost importance to us.

This is GOLDSTRIKEPOKER’S Privacy Policy, which is effective as of March 10th, 2008, and describes how GOLDSTRIKEPOKER collects and uses information from the GOLDSTRIKEPOKER Service and the GOLDSTRIKEPOKER website. GOLDSTRIKEPOKER respects the privacy rights of our users and recognizes the importance of protecting the information collected about you. GOLDSTRIKEPOKER uses your data to administer your account, provide information of interest to you, and to communicate with you. GOLDSTRIKEPOKER stores your data in the United States, and our use of your data is subject to this privacy policy. This Privacy Policy may be amended from time to time. Any such changes will be posted on this page. If we make a significant or material change in the way we use your personal information, the change will be posted on this page thirty (30) days prior to taking effect and registered users will be notified via e-mail. If you have any questions regarding the Privacy Policy, or wish to contact us, please send an email to support@GOLDSTRIKEPOKER.com.

Types of Information Collected

Personally Identifiable Information

Personal information is information that identifies you and may be used to contact you on-line or off-line. GOLDSTRIKEPOKER collects personal information from our online visitors during account registration, or through sign-ups for newsletter subscriptions, referral services, and other marketing surveys and email campaigns.

Information collected will vary depending upon the activity and may include your name, e-mail address, phone number, home address, birth date, and credit card information. For purposes of verifying your identify in case you are a prize winner, we may ask for a copy of photo identification, and social security number (for tax purposes). The photo identification and social security number will be used solely for verification of your identity and for tax purposes. In addition, we may collect demographic information such as gender, zip code, software, platform, Internet IP address and connection, information about your use of the Service such as tournaments played, game play statistics, user rankings and click paths and other data that you may provide in surveys or online profiles. We may combine demographic information with personal information, such as email address, to tailor our offerings or web pages to your preferences or interests. Prize winners may also be required to provide Social Security or other tax identification numbers for tax purposes.

Aggregate Information  
We may store non-personally identifiable information that we collect through log files to create a profile of our users in the aggregate. Log files record internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser types, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks which we will use to analyze trends, administer the Service or GOLDSTRIKEPOKER website, track aggregate service and usage patterns, and gather broad demographic information for general use. Your individual usage cannot be tracked through aggregate data.  
As is standard practice on many web sites, GOLDSTRIKEPOKER may use "cookies" and other technologies to recognize you and provide personalization, as well as to help us understand which parts of our web site is the most popular, where our visitors are going and how much time they spend there.

Online Chat Rooms and Profiles  
You may choose to disclose information, including personal information, about yourself through chat functions, message boards, screen name profiles for public view, or in similar forums on the Service. Information that you disclose through these features is public information, and there is no expectation of privacy or confidentiality there. You should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of those features, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit through these features. Please see our Terms of Service on this point and for other guidelines about posting content on the Service. 

How We Use the Information

Account Maintenance and Transactions  
We use your personal information to maintain your GOLDSTRIKEPOKER account and to provide the Service to you. In addition, the personal information you provide will allow us to alert you to new products, features and enhancements; special offers; upgrade opportunities; and events of interest. We may send you electronic communications about the Service or your Account.

Statistical Analysis  
GOLDSTRIKEPOKER may perform statistical, demographic and marketing analyses of users, and their usage patterns, for product development purposes and to generally inform advertisers about the nature of our user base.

Products and Services from Third Parties  
You may opt in to allow GOLDSTRIKEPOKER to share your personal information with companies and organizations that provide products or services that we believe may be of interest to you. We see this as a value-added service helping you to find useful products or services. We strive to limit use of the information you provide to those offers that we think you would appreciate receiving. You may opt-out of receiving these offers by changing this option in your Account settings. To opt out of further communications from a marketing partner or sponsor with whom your information has been shared while you had opted-in to receiving such communications, please contact that partner directly.

Changing or Updating Your Information  
You can correct or update your account information at any time by logging into the Service and going to your account. Should you be unable to log in or wish to have your account deactivated contact support@GOLDSTRIKEPOKER.com. We will be happy to review, update or remove information as appropriate. We may still retain your information in our files however, to resolve disputes, enforce our terms of use, and due to technical and legal requirements and constraints related to the security, integrity and operation of the Service and our websites.

Security  
The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number numbers) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact support@GOLDSTRIKEPOKER.com.

Public Data  
Your participation in tournaments or other public online events, is conditional upon you agreeing to us collecting, using, storing, transmitting and publicly displaying statistical data (such as your scores, rankings and achievements) generated through your participation.

COPPA Compliance  
GOLDSTRIKEPOKER does not knowingly collect or store any personal information, even in aggregate, about children under the age of 13.

Compliance with Legal Process  
We may disclose personal information if we are required to do so by law or we in good faith believe that such action is necessary to: (1) comply with the law or with legal process; (2) protect and defend our rights and property; (3) protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our the Service or GOLDSTRIKEPOKER web sites; or (4) protect the personal safety or property of our users or the public (among other things, this means that if you provide false information or attempt to pose as someone else, information about you may be disclosed as part of any investigation into your actions).

Terms and Conditions   Refund Policy
